A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Assembly and Senate Memos, Series 3 FA354
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 3297-3578 (Box 33, Folder 299)
- 1963 Senate Internal Memo 3579-3786 (Box 33, Folder 300)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 2-574 (Box 33, Folder 301)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 577-864 (Box 33, Folder 302)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 868-1217 (Box 33, Folder 303)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 1223-1650 (Box 33, Folder 304)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 1677-2166 (Box 33, Folder 305)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 2167-2463 (Box 33, Folder 306)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 2465-2909 (Box 33, Folder 307)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 2923-3303 (Box 34, Folder 308)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 3304-3716 (Box 34, Folder 309)
- 1964 Senate Internal Memo 3729-3919 (Box 34, Folder 310)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 1-552 (Box 34, Folder 311)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 555-969 (Box 34, Folder 312)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 970-1451 (Box 34, Folder 313)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 1470-1802 (Box 34, Folder 314)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 1804-2161 (Box 34, Folder 315)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 2175-2545 (Box 34, Folder 316)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 2551-2908 (Box 35, Folder 317)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 2909-3225 (Box 35, Folder 318)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 3230-3451 (Box 35, Folder 319)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 3452-3829 (Box 35, Folder 320)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 3830-4088 (Box 35, Folder 321)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 4102-4383 (Box 35, Folder 322)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 4384-4572 (Box 35, Folder 323)
- 1965 Senate Internal Memo 4578-4741 (Box 35, Folder 324)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 21-628 (Box 35, Folder 325)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 629-1093 (Box 36, Folder 326)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 1096-1499 (Box 36, Folder 327)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 1526-2049 (Box 36, Folder 328)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 2052-2537 (Box 36, Folder 329)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 2538-2857 (Box 36, Folder 330)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 2859-3174 (Box 36, Folder 331)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 3214-3694 (Box 36, Folder 332)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 3736-4428 (Box 36, Folder 333)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 4434-4679 (Box 36, Folder 334)
- 1966 Senate Internal Memo 4686-5003 (Box 37, Folder 335)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 2-A-536 (Box 37, Folder 336)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 542-903 (Box 37, Folder 337)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 912-A-1657 (Box 37, Folder 338)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 1664-2131 (Box 37, Folder 339)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 2132-2568-A (Box 37, Folder 340)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 2575-3075 (Box 37, Folder 341)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 3098-A-3479 (Box 37, Folder 342)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 3510-4025 (Box 37, Folder 343)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 4030-A-4445 (Box 38, Folder 344)
- 1967 Senate Internal Memo 4446-4645 (Box 38, Folder 345)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 3-A-659-A (Box 38, Folder 346)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 661-1293=A (Box 38, Folder 347)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 1303-A-1839 (Box 38, Folder 348)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 1847-2594 (Box 38, Folder 349)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 2597-3106 (Box 38, Folder 350)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 3107-3620 (Box 38, Folder 351)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 3621-3989-A (Box 38, Folder 352)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 3996-A-4499 (Box 39, Folder 353)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 4503-A-5035-A (Box 39, Folder 354)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 5060-5368 (Box 39, Folder 355)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 5369-5601 (Box 39, Folder 356)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 5604-A-5736-A (Box 39, Folder 357)
- 1968 Senate Internal Memo 5739-5951 (Box 39, Folder 358)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 2-612 (Box 39, Folder 359)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 634-A-1017 (Box 39, Folder 360)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 1018-A-1440 (Box 39, Folder 361)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 1442-1890 (Box 40, Folder 362)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 1891-2143-A (Box 40, Folder 363)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 2150-2515 (Box 40, Folder 364)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 2517-3010-A (Box 40, Folder 365)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 3014-3538-B (Box 40, Folder 366)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 3540-4066 (Box 40, Folder 367)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 4076-4405 (Box 40, Folder 368)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 4406-4883 (Box 40, Folder 369)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 4884-A-5229 (Box 40, Folder 370)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 5237-5507 (Box 41, Folder 371)
- 1969 Senate Internal Memo 5508-5694 (Box 41, Folder 372)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 147-3851 (Box 41, Folder 373)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 3871-A-5912 (Box 41, Folder 374)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 5913-6383 (Box 41, Folder 375)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 6392-6851 (Box 41, Folder 376)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 6858-7193 (Box 41, Folder 377)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 7201-7517 (Box 41, Folder 378)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 7521-A-7998 (Box 41, Folder 379)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 8002-B-8525 (Box 42, Folder 380)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 8526-A-8816 (Box 42, Folder 381)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 8822-A-9156 (Box 42, Folder 382)
- 1970 Senate Internal Memo 9161-9484 (Box 42, Folder 383)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 3-879 (Box 42, Folder 384)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 902-C-1684 (Box 42, Folder 385)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 1691-B-2417-A (Box 42, Folder 386)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 2429-A-3284-A (Box 42, Folder 387)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 3291-3730 (Box 42, Folder 388)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 3733-4197-B (Box 43, Folder 389)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 4201-4572 (Box 43, Folder 390)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 4585-4958 (Box 43, Folder 391)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 4975-5510-C (Box 43, Folder 392)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 5513-5746 (Box 43, Folder 393)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 5784-A-6302-A (Box 43, Folder 394)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 6304-6585 (Box 43, Folder 395)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 6587-6822 (Box 43, Folder 396)
- 1971 Senate Internal Memo 6824-7070 (Box 43, Folder 397)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 110-5430-A (Box 44, Folder 398)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 5491-7265 (Box 44, Folder 399)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 7278-A-7576-B (Box 44, Folder 400)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 7582-A-7898-A (Box 44, Folder 401)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 7910-A-8181 (Box 44, Folder 402)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 8196-A-8496-A (Box 44, Folder 403)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 8497-8785 (Box 44, Folder 404)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 8794-9441-A (Box 44, Folder 405)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 9442-9768 (Box 44, Folder 406)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 9772-10046 (Box 44, Folder 407)
- 1972 Senate Internal Memo 10318-10560 (Box 45, Folder 408)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 6-907-A (Box 45, Folder 409)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 908-1323 (Box 45, Folder 410)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 1330-1732-A (Box 45, Folder 411)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 1737-2288-A (Box 45, Folder 412)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 2309-3032-A (Box 45, Folder 413)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 3038-B-3513 (Box 45, Folder 414)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 3514-4179 (Box 45, Folder 415)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 4183-4589 (Box 46, Folder 416)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 4613-A-5228 (Box 46, Folder 417)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 5235-A-5938-B (Box 46, Folder 418)
- Not Used (Box 46, Folder 419)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 5950-A-6216 (Box 46, Folder 420)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 6221-6476 (Box 46, Folder 421)
- 1973 Senate Internal Memo 6487-6638 (Box 46, Folder 422)
- Memoranda of Law (1) (Box 46, Folder 423)
- Memoranda of Law (2) (Box 46, Folder 424)